Lesson 15.50 Pents worth of trouble.
第15章的款项价值。
appreciate: v.   欣赏，感激
Children always appreciate small gifts of money.
孩子们总是欣赏小礼物。
Mom or dad, of course, provide a regular supply of pocket money.
当然，爸爸妈妈可以定期提供零用钱。
But uncles and aunts are always a source of extra income.
但是叔叔和阿姨始终是额外收入的来源。
With some children, small sums go a long way.
有了一些孩子，小额款项走了很长一段路。
If 50 pens pieces are not exchanged for sweets,
如果没有将50件笔换成糖果，
they rattle for months inside money boxes.
他们在金钱盒中拨动了几个月。
thrifty: adj. 节约的
Only very thrifty children manage to fill up a money box.
只有非常节俭的孩子才能填满钱箱。
For most of them, 50 pens is a small price to pay for a nice big bar of chocolate.
对于他们中的大多数人来说，50支笔是为了支付一块漂亮的大巧克力的小代价。
nephew: n.   侄子，外甥
My nephew, George, has a money box but it is always empty.
我的侄子乔治（George）有一个钱盒，但它总是空的。
Very few of the 50 pens pieces and pound coins I have given him have found their way there.
我给他的50件笔和磅硬币中很少有人在那里找到了他们的路。
I gave him 50 pens yesterday and advised him to save it.
昨天我给了他50支笔，并建议他保存它。
Instead he bought himself 50 pens worth of trouble.
取而代之的是，他买了50张子的麻烦。
bounce: v.   弹起，跳起, pavement: n.   人行道
On his way to the sweet shop, he dropped his 50 pens and it bounced along the pavement
在去甜店的途中，他丢下了50支笔，然后沿着人行道弹跳
and then disappeared down a drain.
然后消失在排水管上。
George took off his jacket, rolled up his sleeves and pushed his right arm through the drain cover.
乔治脱下外套，卷起袖子，将右臂推过排水管。
He could not find his 50 pens piece anywhere.
他在任何地方都找不到他的50张笔。
And what is more, he could no get his arm out.
而且，他无法伸出手臂。
A crowd of people gathered around him and a lady rubbed his arm with soap and butter.
一群人聚集在他周围，一位女士用肥皂和黄油擦了手臂。
But George was firmly stuck.
但是乔治被牢牢地陷入了困境。
brigade: n.   旅，（消防）队, grease: n.   润滑油
The fire brigade was called an two firefighter freed George using a special type of grease.
消防队被称为两名消防员使用一种特殊类型的油脂释放乔治。
George was not too upset by his experience because the lady who owns the sweet shop heard about his.
乔治并不为自己的经历而沮丧，因为拥有甜蜜店的女士听说了他。
Troubles and rewarded him with large box of chocolates.
麻烦，用大盒巧克力奖励他。